<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Mark That Pawn</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.MarkThatPawn</packageId>
  <author>Mlie</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/MarkThatPawn</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/iCj5o7O.png[/img]

You get a large raid and looking through the pawns you find one that would be excellent to capture, but sadly you lose them in the action. You later find their corpse blown up by one of your rockets.

With this mod you can mark any pawn with a selection of icons to make them easier to keep track of.

Mod-options:
[list]
[*]Change the size and position of the icon
[*]Change the icon-set used 
[*]Relative icon-size based on pawn-size
[*]Increase the icon-size when zoomed out, selectable strength
[*]Have different icon-sets based on the pawn type
[*]Disable the gizmos based on the pawn type
[*]Have the icons pulse like the question mark over traders in a caravan
[*]Show all applicable icons
[*]Rotating the active icon between the applicable icons
[*]Show all icons when hovering the icons or selecting the pawn
[/list]

You can define rules to make spawning pawns get marked automatically. The rules are defined based on:
[list]
[*]Weapons equipped
[*]Weapon type equipped
[*]Apparels equipped
[*]Apparel type equipped
[*]Pawn skill levels
[*]Pawn traits
[*]Pawn age
[*]Pawn gender
[*]Relations to colonists
[*]Pawn category
[*]Pawn has one or more permanent hediffs, like a bionic limb
[*]Pawn has any bad permanent hediff, like a scar
[*]Animal type
[*]Faction icon
[*]Ideology icon (Ideology)
[*]Xenotype (Biotech)
[*]Genes (Biotech)
[/list]

There are also priority rules that get applied based on events
[list]
[*]Pawn is drafted
[*]Pawn is in a mental state
[*]Pawn has one or more temporary hediffs, like an injury
[/list]

If you have [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2895299310]TD Find Lib[/url] active you can add rules that uses its search filters. These filters are saved in the save-game so they require and active game to add or edit.

All applicable rules can also be set to only apply to one category of pawns.

There are default sets of icons for each type of pawn but you can always set any icon for a specific pawn using the custom option. There is also support for vehicles using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=3014915404]Vehicle Framework[/url].

It is very simple to add more Icon-sets as only a small xml-definition is needed to make it be selectable in the mod options. If you have suggestions for new icon-sets or new rules, please leave a comment here or on the Discord server and Ill see if I can add it to the mod!

Mod-idea: Cedric

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/MarkThatPawn][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Ds0rBAD.png[/img]
Since modding is just a hobby for me I expect no donations to keep modding. If you still want to show your support you can gift me anything from my [url=https://store.steampowered.com/wishlist/id/Mlie]Wishlist[/url] or buy me a cup of tea.

[url=https://ko-fi.com/G2G55DDYD][img]https://i.imgur.com/VWG0yff.png[/img][/url]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/5xwDG6H.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/3056996662][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/MarkThatPawn?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;labelColor=0070cd&amp;color=white[/img][/url]</description>
</ModMetaData>